紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   國士章魚X
翻譯   杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯   蘇小黛
翻譯   吃冰棒
翻譯   肉松
翻譯   Lynn_寧
翻譯   鹽湖涼開水
時間軸   Ans
時間軸   念念
時間軸   王者蔥
后期   餓得慌
顧問   老杜
校對   草草
總監   草草
紙牌屋
人人影視傾情奉獻
第五季  第三集
康威
戰爭英雄
戰爭
不是兒戲
波利跳
威爾·康威與美國面對面
俄亥俄州克利夫蘭
#問康威
威爾·康威與美國面對面
田納西州克拉克斯維爾
#問康威
威爾·康威與美國面對面
華盛頓特區
華盛頓  白宮
道·斯
以防你不明白這是怎么回事
In case you have no idea what's going on,
我要擴充這些州的國民警衛隊
I'm swelling these states' National Guard troops
以確保選舉日公共場合的安全性
to create secure public spaces on Election Day.
對投票站增加警力
The voting centers with the added law enforcement,
能充分保證
will give us everything that we need
選舉的安全性
to protect the integrity of the ballot box.
總統的做法很聰明
It's smart, what the president's doing.
為他的民調加了分
It's serving him in the polls.
你們還記得馬修斯吧
You remember Matthews, don't you?
加勒特·沃克總統的前副總統
Former vice president to President Garrett Walker.
州長愿意讓過去成為往事
The governor is willing to let the past stay in the past.
希望這樣一來我能指望上你
I hope that means that I can count on you.
我們是一個小型兄弟會的  都是前副總統
We're members of a tiny brotherhood, you and I, of ex-VPs.
我倒是找到了段主席幕僚長的色情報復視頻
I did find some revenge porn on the chairman's chief of staff.
我想跟你上司談談宣戰委員會的事
I wanna talk to your boss about the Declaration of War Committee.
你就是個畜生
You're a pig.
讓他獲得紫心勛章的那次行動  格外突出
The incident for which he was awarded the Purple Heart stands out.
這表明了他能成為怎樣的三軍統帥
Speaks to the kind of commander in chief he will be.
我希望
I'd appreciate it
你別提起我戰斗記錄的細節
if you didn't bring up the details of my combat record.
一個從沒服過役的人
A man who's never served.
哪怕戰爭咬上他的屁股
Wouldn't know what a real war was
他都認不出來
if it jumped up and bit him in the ass.
美國應該盡早聽聽他立功的來龍去脈
Someday soon, America needs to hear the full story of that day.
我找不到合適的語言形容那天發生的事
I don't have the right words for what happened that day.
但毋庸置疑他是位英雄
But he was a hero, no question.
康威上尉的行為是英勇的
Captain Conway's conduct was heroic.
一位英雄
A hero.
塔利班劫持了陸軍上尉克雷格·斯夸爾
Army Captain Craig Squire had been captured by the Taliban,
他被關在坎大哈省
held hostage in the Kandahar province.
我們發現情報有誤
We realized the intel was bad.
我們找到他時  已開始遭受火力
By the time we found him, we'd started taking fire.
那里就像是死亡花園
It was like a death garden or something.
康威上尉跑下飛機  把斯夸爾救了出來
Captain Conway got out of the plane and got Squire out.
別問我過程有多艱辛
Don't even ask me how.
這次選舉太重要了
This election is too important.
是選弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
You have a choice between Francis Underwood
還是選真正的英雄
and a real hero.
當你濫用"戰爭"這個詞  事情就會變成這樣
This is what happens when you throw around a word like "War."
全都亂作一團
All hell breaks loose.
他救了斯夸爾  他救了我們所有人
He saved Squire. He saved all of us.
戰爭不是兒戲
War is real.
本視頻由"美國人尋求真理"出資制作
Paid for by Americans for Truth.
我不知道我們得說多少遍
I don't know how many times I have to go through this,
但我的競選團隊跟那條廣告一點關系都沒有
but my campaign had nothing to do with that ad.
是超級政治行動委員會做的
That was a super PAC.
-我知道  但是  -但那些士兵
- I know, but-- - But those soldiers, though.
他們才是英雄
They're the ones.
這個國家欠他們太多了
This country owes them a lot.
-但那條廣告成天在播  -你想知道原因嗎
- But that ad is on all the time. - You wanna know why?
因為弗蘭克·安德伍德沒能保護這個國家的安全
Because Frank Underwood has failed to keep this country safe.
詹姆斯·米勒之死
The death of James Miller,
所謂的哈里發國對東首都電信的攻擊
the so-called ICO attack at Capital East Telecom network...
等等  你是說哈里發國不是罪魁禍首
Wait, wait, wait. Are you saying ICO wasn't responsible?
我是說這不重要
I'm saying it doesn't matter.
網絡通訊在總統眼皮底下癱瘓掉了
The Internet went down on the president's watch.
-你不覺得哈里發國  -聽著  弗萊德
- Don't you think ICO was-- - Now listen, Fred--
不  哈里發國才是真正的威脅
No, ICO is a real threat.
還有很多人在等
There's a lot of people waiting
說好每個人問一個問題的
and I promised one question per person.
能跟你談話很高興
It was great talking to you,
明天別忘了去投票
and please don't forget to vote tomorrow.
我們進行了多久了
Now, how long have we been going, anyway?
-四個小時  -四個小時
- Four hours. - Four hours.
那么還得再戰二十個小時
That means we got 20 hours to go
我還沒來得及感謝波利跳的朋友們
and I haven't even had the chance to thank my friends at Pollyhop
感謝他們促成了這一切  并直播這一活動
for making this all possible and live streaming this event.
感謝本杰明·格蘭特和他的團隊
Benjamin Grant and his crew.
好了  下一個問題是什么
All right. What's the next question?
安妮  緬因州的安妮  你想問什么
Annie? Annie from Maine. What's on your mind?
弗萊德是我們的人嗎
Was Fred one of ours?
我覺得是  我們得繼續挑那條廣告的刺
I think so. We're gonna keep hitting the ad.
莉安安排好了提問的人  你到了嗎
LeAnn's got callers lined up. Are you there yet?
快了  然后再回飛機上
Almost. Then back on the plane.
-我要繼續了  -還是在俄亥俄嗎
- I'm about to go on. - Ohio, still?
是啊  他看上去怎么樣  康威
Oh, yeah. And how's he looking? Conway?
他才直播了四個小時  他堅持不下去的
Well, he's only four hours in. It's not sustainable.
但他是不是氣勢逼人
But is he commanding?
他很傲慢  弗蘭西斯
He's arrogant, Francis.
-總統先生  -我得掛了
- Mr. President? - I have to go.
好  葛底斯堡見
Okay. See you in Gettysburg.
你是說  要是安德伍德
You're saying it doesn't matter
知道賄賂的事也沒關系
if Underwood knew about pay-for-play?
我是說  那無論如何都不好
Well, I'm saying it's bad either way.
他要么是從他自己黨派的人那兒偷來了總統之位
He either stole the presidency from his own party,
要么是在腐敗的政府中做了副總統
or he was vice president in a corrupt administration.
但我們應該讓委員會做好本職工作
But it's important that we let the committee do its job.
感謝你的來電  安妮
So thanks for your call, Annie.
夏威夷德拉海灘的亞瑟·卡波  亞瑟  你好嗎
Arthur Capo from Del Rey Beach, Hawaii. Arthur, how you doing?
他們為什么想跟你說話
Why did they want to talk to you?
抱歉  誰  你的問題是什么  亞瑟
I'm sorry, who? Uh, what's your question, Arthur?
約書·馬斯特森和扎克瑞
Josh Masterson and Zachary...
我忘了他姓什么  殺害吉姆·米勒的恐怖分子
I forget his last name. But the terrorists who killed Jim Miller.
好  那個
Right. Uh, well...
我只知道他們的一系列要求
All I know is what they said in their list of demands.
他們相信我會當選  成為總統
And they believed I would be elected president.
但說真的  為什么  為什么是你
But really, why? Why you?
我與他們的談判
I successfully negotiated
成功救出了卡洛琳和梅莉莎·米勒
the release of Caroline and Melissa Miller.
-但沒救成吉姆·米勒  -我沒得到機會
- But not Jim Miller. - I wasn't given the chance.
他回答問題的方式  你怎么看
What's your read on him, the way he answers those questions?
-他有所隱瞞  -是嗎
- He's hiding something. - Right.
但這無所謂
But it doesn't matter.
他很現代  讓總統不那么高高在上
He's modern. He makes the presidency accessible.
你難道不想看到總統候選人通宵連線嗎
I mean, don't you want to see the candidate stay up all night?
你是說弗蘭西斯老了嗎
Are you calling Francis old?
多謝各位熱情的掌聲  女士們先生們
I appreciate the applause, ladies and gentlemen,
但我知道你們是在為你們想見的那個女人鼓掌
but I imagine it's for the woman you really came to see.
"這是危機四伏的時刻"
"These are dangerous times."
現在確實危機四伏
These are dangerous times.
副總統候選人
...of the United States,
克萊爾·安德伍德
Claire Underwood.
要知道  他只比我大幾歲
He's only a couple years older than me, you know.
謝謝  謝謝你們  內華達
Thank you. Thank you, Nevada!
我非常感謝你們一大早來到這里
I really appreciate you all coming out here this morning.
零售式競選真是無可替代
No substitute for retail politics.
尤其是她的形象
Especially her brand.
謝謝
Thank you.
能請你給我拿杯水嗎
Could you get me some water, please?
大家好啊
Hello, everyone.
非常感謝
Thank you so much.
謝謝你們  你們真是太好了
Thank you very much. That's very kind.
非常感謝
Oh, thanks so much.
別鼓掌了
Oh, now stop that.
停下吧  別鼓了  夠啦夠啦
Stop it, stop it. Enough, enough, enough. Enough.
我都臉紅了  這么吹捧我
It's embarrassing, all of that adulation.
你好  很高興見到你  謝謝你能來
Hello, nice to see you. Thank you so much for coming out.
非常感謝
Much appreciated.
-杰克  -演講很成功  總統先生
- Jack! - Great speech, Mr. President.
你真是把我的心里話說出來了
It's like you're saying what I'm thinking.
這就對了  謝謝
Well, that is the idea. Thank you.
不過話說康威的事有點讓我擔心啊
Uh, I'm a little worried about the Conway thing, though.
提起了好多問題
Bringing up a lot of questions.
但沒得到多少回答
But not a lot of answers.
我們也不想在大選投票日前一天
Yeah, and we don't need to keep hearing about that article
老提起那篇文章吧
the day before the election.
有什么辦法嗎
What are we doing about it?
我們聚在這里了  杰克
Well, we're here, Jack.
我們要多握手  能扳回一個算一個
We are fighting back one handshake at a time.
格溫多林  你今天真是太美了
Gwendolyn, you look absolutely stunning.
能麻煩給我照張相嗎  史蒂夫
May I get a photograph, please, Steve?
麻煩你  千萬別把他照進去
Could you do this, please? Make sure you cut him out.
接下來是來自德州科珀斯克里斯蒂的杰弗
We have Jeff from Corpus Christi, Texas.
你今天怎么樣  杰弗
How are you doing today, Jeff?
我們看到那條營救行動的廣告了
We saw the ad. About the rescue.
杰弗啊  這個話題我前面已經說過了
You know, Jeff, I feel like we have been through this already.
您救了我哥哥的命  先生
You saved my brother's life, sir.
克雷格·斯夸爾
Craig Squire.
斯夸爾上尉  就是你哥哥
Captain Squire. That's... that's your brother?
上尉
Captain.
還記得我嗎
Remember me?
我記得  我當然記得
I do remember. Of course I remember.
我以為你不愿重提舊事
I didn't think you wanted talk about it.
我們挺過來了  就夠了  是不是
We lived through it. That's enough, isn't it?
我一直沒機會感謝你  告訴你
I never got to thank you and tell you...
斯夸爾上尉  換了你也會救我的
Captain Squire, you would've done the same.
我不知道  我當時在那里
I don't know. I was in there.
他們朝我身上扔尸體  一個接一個
They were tossing bodies on top of me, one after the other...
我死定了
I was already dead.
不對  就好像我已經死了一次
That's not right. It's like I've been dead once already.
但那些尸體  就那么堆在一起
But the bodies... the way they were stuck together.
又那么熱  還有味道
And the heat and the smell...
但你還記得你把我拉出來的時候嗎
But you know when you were pulling me out, remember?
我其實記不太清楚了
I... I don't remember much, actually.
一切都發生得太快了
It all happened pretty quick.
我知道你聽見了
I know you heard it.
你得打斷這個問題
You have to get him out of this question.
他不喜歡提這些事  你知道的
You know he doesn't like talking about this. You know that.
-漢娜  -得了
- Hannah, - Come on, man.
-我們談談  -你肯定聽見了
- let's talk. - I know you did.
我當時只想盡快把咱們救出去
I was just trying to get us out of there as fast as I could.
克雷格  我們活下來了
Craig, we're here.
-我們挺過來了  -是  可是
- We made it. - Yeah, but...
你得繼續生活
You gotta live your life.
謝謝您接我們的電話
Thanks for taking our call.
謝謝
Thank you.
他說的程度還不夠  他沒讓康威...
He didn't call him out enough. He didn't get Conway to--
聽著  他盡力了
Look... he did what he could.
他聽到了什么  他那是什么意思
What did he hear? What did he mean by that?
不知道  那是威爾和他之間的事
I don't know. It's between Will and him.
他早就想讓威爾出來說清楚了  不過
He's wanted Will to come clean about it for a long time, but...
沒能如愿
it didn't happen.
所以  看在克雷格的分上
Which is why, for Craig's sake,
我們得讓他們再連線一次
we need to get them back on the phone.
哈維小姐  你跟了我們幾個月了
Miss Harvey, you've been on us for months.
抱歉沒能成功
I'm sorry it didn't work out.
如果這意味著交易取消  沒事
If this means the deal's off, okay.
我們總能找個去處
We can always find a place to go.
讓我再跟他談談  我們可不希望他
Just let me talk to him again. We wouldn't want him to--
天啊  我哥哥經歷得夠多了
Jesus Christ! My brother has been through enough.
我們不干了
We're done.
請你離開
I need you to leave.
他做得很好
He's doing great.
是嗎
Is he?
那廣告對我們有好處
That ad's playing for us.
聽著  我是同意了
Look, I... I agreed to this.
-但我了解我丈夫  -我知道
- But I know my husband. - I know you do.
那些問題是意料之中的  對嗎
And those questions were to be expected, yes?
斯夸爾改了主意是好事
It's a good thing Squire changed his mind.
我們今晚可以調出一些帶子  拼湊點什么出來
We can pull some tape and put something together tonight.
明早上放出來
Hit some markets in the morning.
等到了投票的時候
When it's time to vote...
威爾救了他的命
Will saved his life.
太過了
This is too much.
我不想再聽到關于那場戰爭的問題了
I don't want any more questions about the war.
不行的
That's not gonna work.
聽著  我可以給你看數據
Look, I can show you numbers,
可以給你看這對我們多有利
I can show you how well it's all playing for us.
我只是說  馬克  這是...
What I'm saying, Mark, is that this--
我做這行很久了  漢娜
I've been at this a long time, Hannah.
知道嗎  當馬歇爾告訴我你有空時
You know, when Marshall told me you were available--
馬歇爾和我是老相識了
Marshall and I go way back.
這時機對我們所有人都合適  對嗎
The timing is right for all of us, right?
我們非常感激
We're very grateful.
那他就會告訴你  我通常不會
Then he will tell you, I don't get involved,
在這么晚的時候插進來
not this late in the game, unless
除非我知道我能發揮影響
I know I can make a difference.
所以不管威爾和斯夸爾發生了什么
So whatever happened to Will with Squire, whatever...
-不是  -我不想知道  也不需要知道
- It's not-- - I don't wanna know. I don't need to know.
但不管那些事讓他承受著怎樣的痛苦
But whatever pain he's carrying about what happened...
對我們是有利的
it's working for us.
所以  我需要你
So, this is what I need from you.
回去那里
To go back out there
確保他能撐到明早
and just make sure he makes it through until morning.
他有機會做一個好總統
He has a chance to be a fine president.
一個偉大的總統
A great president.
那更好了
Even better.
因為我們需要這樣的總統
Because we could use one.
斯夸爾沒出現在那廣告里是有原因的
There's a reason that Squire didn't appear in that ad.
我還在確認細節
I'm just nailing down the specifics.
-讓道格加入吧  -他在去費城的路上
- Let's bring Doug in on this. - He's on his way to Philly.
而且恕我直言  先生
And with all due respect, sir,
他的技能在這里并不適用
his skill set doesn't necessarily apply here.
你知道道格跟我多久了嗎  莉安
Do you know how long Doug has worked for me, LeAnn?
不太清楚
Not exactly, no.
幾乎是一輩子了
Well, it's just this side of forever.
我了解他的一切
I know everything about him.
他的優勢  他的弱點  他的技能
His strengths, his weaknesses, his skill set
以及他心里在想什么
and the contents of his soul.
希望您不是在質疑我的忠誠
I hope you're not questioning my loyalty.
我只是想了解為我工作的人  莉安
I just like to know about the people who work for me, LeAnn.
-我很坦誠的  -我根本不信
- I'm pretty straightforward. - I don't believe that for a second.
我第一次跟道格坐下來談
The first time I sat down with Doug,
更像是他的坦白而非對話
it was more of a confession than a conversation.
他跟我說了他酗酒的事  他的過去
He told me about his drinking, his past.
他對我徹底敞開了心扉
He was completely open with me.
我不覺得我們能指望克雷格·斯夸爾
I don't think we can rely on Craig Squire.
那我們還有什么好說的
Then why am I still talking to you?
我沒有掩飾內心  先生
I'm not hiding the contents of my soul, sir.
去找凡妮莎·莫里森
Reach out to Vanessa Morrison.
我已經聯系總監了
I already reached out to the director.
對  但道格還沒有
Yes, but Doug hasn't.
讓他去做  你在康威結束他的小節目前
So have him do it and then you come up with something else
想點別的點子出來
before Conway is done with his little sideshow.
關于接下來的演講
And in terms of what comes next,
我調整了開場白  縮減了正文的篇幅
I adjusted the opening remarks and cut some from the stump.
正文不用改了
The stump is just fine.
非常感謝
Thank you very much.
請給我接第一夫人
Get me the First Lady, please.
這個嘛  簡單來說就是
Well, the... the short answer is
在民主體制下  每個人都有相同的權利
in a democracy, everyone has the same rights...
和相同的機會
the same opportunities.
喂
Hello.
我們身邊的人知道風險有多大嗎
Do the people around us understand what it takes?
我知道康威的聲勢起來了
Look, I know Conway's getting a bump,
但這不代表接下來的一天里我們不能扳回來
but it doesn't mean we can't surmount it in the next 24 hours.
他們知道我們付出了多少才走到今天
Do they know what we have done to get this far?
湯姆現在就坐在我對面
Tom is sitting across from me right now.
我才不管你對面坐著誰  克萊爾
I don't care who you're sitting next to, Claire.
我們都在拼盡全力  全速拉票
We're all doing everything we can as fast as we can.
我不喜歡  我不喜歡追趕別人
I don't like it. I don't like chasing this.
你下一站去哪
What's your next stop?
-我們20分鐘到斯克蘭頓  -你得養養嗓子
- We, uh... We're in Scranton in 20. - You need to save your voice.
我們戰場上見
I'll see you on the battlefield.
總統怎么樣
How's the President doing?
他還把自己當個年輕人
He's acting like he's still 30 years old.
我們都是
We both are.
這是好事  還是壞事
Is that good... or bad?
得看我們是輸是贏了
That depends on if we win or lose.
因為我是個老兵
Because I'm a vet
我還是沒弄清楚到底怎么回事
and I'm still not clear on exactly what happened.
我覺得具體情況
You know, I think everything
當時在場的士兵已經說得很清楚了
has been said by the soldiers who were there.
不對  你的飛機
No. 'Cause your plane,
是被擊落還是按計劃去營救
was it shot down or was it a planned rescue?
是計劃的
Planned, yes.
但是后來計劃不得不調整了
Until the plan had to change.
-我想你懂的  -我不懂  先生
- I think you get the idea. - No, I don't get it, sir.
-你是飛行員吧  -對
- You were a pilot, right? - Yes.
那你為什么會出艙執行地面任務
So why were your boots even on the ground?
我們的情報有誤
Our intel was flawed.
情報有誤  我只得介入  沒辦法
Our intel was flawed and I... I had to step in. I had to.
你好  麥克
Hi, Mike.
我丈夫是個謙虛的人
My husband is a humble man.
你是不會聽到他那天英勇救人的全部過程的
You're never going to get the details of his bravery that day.
至少他自己不會說
At least, not from him.
在我看來  他的戰友說得好
To me, his comrades say it all.
威爾是個有能力應對任何狀況的人
Will is a man who is equipped to deal with whatever comes at him.
而現在  我想和你說一件更重要的事
And now, I'd like to put in a word on a more practical matter,
這些新集中選民的投票中心
these new centralized voting centers.
因為最近我們收到了許多來電和疑問
Because we've had lots of calls and questions.
無論你支持哪位候選人
Whichever candidate you support,
你一定要去投票  這至關重要
it's essential that you get out to vote.
搭鄰居的車  或者聯系當地的黨務辦公室
Ask a neighbor for a ride or call your local party office.
這場競選太激烈  決不能掉以輕心
This race is too close for complacency.
我選你
You got my vote!
-安德伍德  -非常感謝
- Underwood! - Thank you so much.
謝謝  謝謝你們
Thank you. Thank you.
太謝謝你們了  謝謝
Thank you so much. Thank you.
謝謝
Oh, thank you.
能麻煩你再給我拿杯蜂蜜茶嗎
Could you also get me a tea with honey, please?
-你這樣還能演講嗎  -我沒事
- Are you gonna be all right to speak? - Yeah, I'm fine.
-聽聽你的嗓子  弗蘭西斯  -別說了
- Listen to your voice, Francis. - Stop.
你這幾天一直連軸轉地跑
You have been running yourself into the ground,
好幾天都沒睡了
you haven't slept for days.
要不你給演講開個頭
Why don't you kick off the speech,
然后交給我  我給大家解釋
let me take over, and then I will explain to...
解釋說總統失聲了嗎
That the president's lost his voice?
不行  你不能這么說
No, you're not gonna say that.
這么關鍵的時候  可不能出這種大新聞
We're not gonna have that headline as we enter the final stretch.
尤其那個蘭斯洛特似的小白臉在那兒嘚吧個沒完
Especially since Sir Lancelot is out there yapping all day long.
我倒不覺得康威是蘭斯洛特
I'm not really sure that Conway's a Sir Lancelot.
是嗎  那你覺得誰是
Oh, really? Then who would you assign that role to?
吐得我真心疼  過來一下
God, I hate to waste that. Excuse me.
隊伍里有個年輕人
There was a young man in line,
在大廳另一邊  差不多靠著第二扇門
on the other side, sort of against that second door.
大概一米八
Six foot tall...
-讓我們單獨說句話吧  -好啊
- Maybe just give us a moment. - Sure.
你能不能試試搞到聯系方式
Can you see if you can get some contact information?
要是能的話把他叫出來  謝謝
Or pull him out if you can. Thank you.
我不是想接管  我是說我們應該以搭檔形象示人
I didn't mean take over. I just meant let's appear as a ticket.
-"團結還是分裂"  -弗蘭西斯
- "Are we united or are we divided?" - Francis--
"就在葛底斯堡這里  最血腥的戰役之一"
"Here at Gettysburg, one of the bloodiest battles--"
我會背你的講稿
I know your speech.
但你能結尾嗎  你得知道怎么結尾  克萊爾
But can you finish? You have to know how to finish, Claire.
我十分榮幸地向大家介紹
I have the distinct honor of introducing you to,
如果一切順利的話
God-willing and the creek don't rise,
美國現任也是下一任總統
the current and next President of the United States of America,
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
Francis Underwood!
謝謝
Thank you.
謝謝  溫特斯議員
Thank you, Congressman Winters,
謝謝  賓夕法尼亞
and thank you, Pennsylvania.
還要感謝我的競選搭檔  妻子
And my running mate, my wife,
摯友和伴侶  克萊爾·安德伍德
and my friend and my partner, Claire Underwood.
跟道格·斯坦普講話我總是有時間的
I've always got a few minutes for Doug Stamper.
再次抱歉  讓你久等了
Again, sorry to keep you waiting.
真的不用給你拿點什么嗎
You sure I can't offer you something?
我不喝酒  州長
I don't drink, Governor.
我有蘇打水  湯力水
Well, I got club soda, tonic...
你說你會建立投票中心
You said you were going to establish voting centers.
沒錯  我試過了
I was. I tried.
說出來你都不信  選區負責人
I got pushback from the precinct captains
給了我多大阻力
like you wouldn't believe.
-你說你會派警衛隊  -那我也試過了
- You said you were gonna deploy troops. - I tried that, too.
我跟美國公民自由聯盟的羅杰·弗蘭克提了
I floated the order past Roger Frank at the ACLU.
他跟黑人聯盟的巴尼·萊納德說了
He mentioned it to Barney Leonard at the Black Coalition.
兩小時內  我就接到八個怒氣沖沖的電話
And within two hours, I got eight angry phone calls
告訴我  要是保護遠郊地區
telling me exactly what would happen
而不保護費城  會發生什么
if I chose to protect exurban areas instead of Philly.
你最好別騙我  州長
You don't want to lie to me, Governor.
我剛從巴尼·萊納德的辦公室過來
I just came from Barney Leonard's office.
-你想改口嗎  -拜托
- You wanna change your story? - Please.
巴尼會告訴你  他威脅挑起種族暴亂
Barney's gonna tell you that he threatened a fucking race riot.
你眼睛都不眨一下地
You fucking lied, straight up,
對美國總統撒謊了
to the President of the United States.
道格
Doug.
-請接巴尼·萊納德的辦公室  -把電話放下
- Barney Leonard's office, please. - Put the phone down.
我是道格·斯坦普
It's Doug Stamper.
對  我需要再找他一次
Yes, I need him one more time.
好吧  掛電話吧
Fine. Hang it up.
我會安排警衛隊的
I'll get you your troops.
你想知道真相嗎
You want the truth?
不感興趣  我已經知道了
Not interested. I had that coming in.
結束了
It's over.
安德伍德明天必輸無疑  他完蛋了
Underwood's gonna lose tomorrow. He's done.
他一完蛋  你也完了
And when he's done, you're done.
你將一無所有  到那時  你就會消失
You'll have nothing left. And then, you'll just disappear.
感謝你抽時間  州長
Thank you for your time, Governor.
要是想把賓州的
What would it take to
國民警衛隊收歸政府所管  需要怎么做
federalize the National Guard in Pennsylvania?
總統讓我給他找些
The president asked me to get him some information
艾瑞克·羅林斯的資料
about Eric Rawlings.
-誰  -葛底斯堡集會的
- Who? - From the Gettysburg event.
我來交給他
I'll give it to him.
穆罕默德·卡拉比  34歲  敘利亞公民
Muhammed Kalabi, 34, Syrian national.
當地線人確認  他的身份可信度很高
Local assets confirm his ID with high confidence.
卡拉比和哈里發國聯系非常緊密
Kalabi has strong connections to ICO.
去年秋天的貝魯特爆炸案
Bombing in Beirut last fall.
貝魯特事件一個月之前
A month before Beirut,
在開羅和艾哈邁迪在一起
with Ahmadi, in Cairo.
先生  現在在美國
Currently, sir, there are four Muhammed Kalabis
有四個穆罕默德·卡拉比
in the United States.
其中兩個和哈里發國的卡拉比年齡相仿
Two are approximately the same age as the ICO Kalabi,
其中一個三周前從阿富汗經加拿大
and one entered the United States three weeks ago
進入美國境內
from Afghanistan by way of Canada.
他是去看他在田納西州諾克斯維爾
He's visiting his girlfriend in Tennessee
一家書店工作的女朋友
who works at a Knoxville bookstore.
你為什么告訴我這些
So why are you bringing me all this?
你問有什么選擇  先生
You asked for options, sir.
在選舉日當天逮捕穆罕默德·卡拉比
To arrest Muhammed Kalabi on election day?
凱茜  要是他告訴當局
Cathy, what's gonna happen
他不是恐怖分子怎么辦
when he tells the authorities he's the wrong one?
但那就是在選舉日之后了
But that would be after the election--
三四天前也許還可行  凱茜
Well, that might have played three or four days ago, Cathy,
但現在已經太遲了
but now it's too late.
你三四天前就拿到這個了嗎
Did you have this three or four days ago?
如果我拿到了肯定會給你看的  先生
I would have brought it to you, sir.
好吧  先這樣吧
All right, well, let's leave it at that.
請道格進來
Send in Doug.
國務卿要走了
The secretary is just leaving.
這是斯夸爾營救行動的全部資料
That's all we have on the Squire rescue.
很不幸  還不夠多
It's not enough, unfortunately.
先生...
Sir...
馬修斯那邊  我覺得他不會照辦
when it comes to Matthews, I don't believe he'll deliver.
我們奪下主動權吧  我們得保護投票站
Let's take this from his hands. We need to protect the polls.
你不用下命令
The request won't come from you.
你會與這事毫無關聯
The way this thing is built, you're nowhere near it.
稍等一下
Hold on a second.
賓州的票數怎么樣了
How are the numbers in Pennsylvania?
勢頭不錯  但還在誤差范圍內  先生
They're good, but they're well within the margin of error, sir.
我們不希望看起來
So we don't want to look like
像是把一支武裝國民警衛隊
we're shoving an armed unit of National Guards
強加給了吉姆·馬修斯  對嗎
down Jim Matthews' throat, right?
-對  -巴尼·萊納德打給我了
- Right. - So, I got a call from Barney Leonard.
你逼得太緊了  道格
You pushed too hard, Doug.
但聽著  我們有四年來對付馬修斯
But look, we'll have four years to take care of Matthews,
我們會收拾他的
and we will.
但如果有別的辦法呢
But what if there was another way?
我敢說  如果大家都坦誠面對自己
I don't think anybody, if they're honest with themselves,
沒有一個人會說他真的信任安德伍德總統
can say they truly trust President Underwood.
憑什么要信任他
Why should they?
我們國家面臨了如此多的威脅
With so many threats to our country,
現在比任何時候都更得選出...
now it's more important than ever to elect...
四年來重點的偏頗
...four years of misguided priorities,
使共和黨變回了追逐私利的黨派
backing the GOP into soliciting private and special interests.
你知道嗎
You know what?
怎么了
What?
-我想當那種人  -哪種人
- I wanna be that person. - What person?
那種做一個小時就能拍屁股走人的人
The person that does this for, like, an hour and then leaves.
不是那樣....
That's not what this--
道格  我的性經歷跟你一樣久
Doug, I've been having sex for as long as you have.
你打給我的時候  我就是這種感覺
And when you called me, that's what it sounded like.
我就想  "好啊"
And I thought, "Great."
可我來了  你在哪里
But I'm here now. Where are you?
我送你回家吧
I should take you home.
不了
No.
-不必勞煩你  -別這樣
- You don't have to. - Come on.
-我自己打車回  -我要送你回家
- I'll take a cab. - I'm taking you home.
你怎么了
What is going on with you?
你說得對  我不該打給你
You're right. I shouldn't have called.
我該回去工作了
I gotta get back to work.
關于新建成的投票站外
Reports are pouring in of protests being staged
發生抗議活動的新聞報道不斷涌入
outside of many of our newly established voting centers.
這引出了一個問題  美國人民
Which begs the question, are Americans fed up
是否已經厭倦了政客們無休止的鬧劇
with our politicians' seemingly unquenchable thirst for conflict?
一邊是安德伍德呼吁正式...
Between Underwood's call for a formal...
想好了嗎
Make a decision?
共和黨的候選人又都是軍人出身
...and the strong military ticket on the Republican side?
巴素·海頓  雙份  不加冰
Basil Hayden's, double, neat.
巴素·海頓
Basil Hayden?
我這兒可沒有  伙計
You're killing me, buddy.
-你有什么  -布萊特是最好的了
- What do you got? - Bulleit's as good as it gets in here.
那就這個吧
I'll have that.
-女人  -工作
- Woman? - Work.
是啊  沒什么是永恒的
Yeah, well, nothing's forever, man.
請那邊那兩位
Those two down there,
還有所有進店的人  花光為止
and anyone else who comes in here until that's gone.
這是給你的
That's for you.
我睡不著
I couldn't sleep.
你的喉嚨不舒服嗎
Is it your throat?
足夠嗎
Is it enough?
我們的努力
What we're doing?
我...
I...
是的
Yes.
那為什么我們沒有遙遙領先
Then why aren't we farther ahead?
大多數的民調顯示...
Most of the polls have us--
我不相信民調
Oh, I don't trust the polls.
除了極少數外  我不相信任何人或任何事
With few exceptions, I don't trust anyone or anything.
投票沒開始前一切都是未知的
We won't know for sure until the vote's begun.
但他們的投票率肯定會降低的
But turnout for their side is sure to be down.
我們今天差點就打敗康威了
We almost had Conway today.
但我們確實傷到了他
And we did some damage.
或許我們不知道他在隱瞞什么
And maybe we don't know what he's hiding,
但公眾知道他有所隱瞞
but the public knows there's something out there.
他睡覺有時會哼歌
He hums in his sleep sometimes.
哼歌
Hums?
哼什么
Like what?
不知道
I don't know.
聽不出來
Nothing recognizable.
他經常哼嗎
Does he do it often?
有時哼
Sometimes.
哼給我聽聽什么樣
Do it for me. What's it sound like?
我給你拿點潤喉的東西
Let's get you something for your throat.
不用  我沒事  你接著睡吧
No, I'm fine. You go back to sleep.
我們明天會成功的  弗蘭西斯
We're gonna get there tomorrow, Francis.
我在一場籌款會上
So, I'm... I'm at this fundraiser.
在阿默甘西特海灘的一幢豪宅里
It's a beautiful house on the beach in Amagansett,
我和一位美女跳了一整夜舞
and I've been dancing all night with this incredible girl,
我完全配不上她
way out of my league.
但當時很晚很晚了
But it's late, very late,
我是個很負責的年輕人
and I'm a very responsible young man, so...
我溜上樓拿我的外套
I sneak upstairs to get my jacket.
但我沒想到...
But lo and behold...
她跟了上來
she's following me.
我看到了走廊鏡子里的自己
And I see my reflection in the hallway mirror and...
我渾身冒汗
I'm just sweating like a pig.
心跳加速
My heart's racing.
她從我身后走來
And she walks up behind me.
我轉身時
And as I turn...
看到了月光映在她的面龐上
I see the moonlight on her face...
一切仿佛都慢了下來
and everything just slows down.
我們就是這樣認識的
And that's how we met.
我和漢娜
Me and Hannah.
很高興并非只有我還在熬夜
Well, I'm glad to hear I'm not the only one up this late.
總統先生  你有問題要問我嗎
Mr. President, do you have a question for me?
不  我沒有  但我可以給你個機會
No, I don't. But I thought I would give you the chance
問我一個問題  只有一個
to ask me a question. Just one.
我不確定我想問你問題
I'm not sure I have any questions for you.
別害羞  威爾
Don't be shy, Will.
畢竟  機會難得
I mean, after all, this is a rare opportunity.
只有你和我
Just between you and me.
只有你和我  還有其他今晚
It's just you and me and all the other Americans out there
失眠的美國人
having trouble sleeping tonight.
那是因為他們知道
Well, that's because they know
明天的投票會決定他們的未來
that tomorrow's vote will decide their future.
這就是關鍵問題  對吧
So that's the question then, isn't it?
未來屬于誰
Who does the future belong to?
我覺得只有上帝能回答那個問題
Well, I don't think anyone but God can answer that one.
我們只能在此生盡可能地證明自己
All we can do is make a case for ourselves while we're here.
好吧
Okay.
我想問你
Here's my question.
我成功的談判
I successfully negotiated
讓卡洛琳和梅莉莎·米勒得以釋放
the release of Caroline and Melissa Miller.
但你插手進來
Then you stepped in.
你沒讓我完成任務  為什么
You didn't let me finish the job. Why?
你真想讓我回答那個問題嗎  威爾
Do you really want me to answer that question, Will?
-我不確定你想這么做  -我很想
- Because I'm not sure you do. - Oh, I do.
因為他們知道自己能夠占你便宜
Because they knew they could take advantage of you.
他們發現了
They saw it.
-怎么說  先生  -他們察覺出來了
- How's that, sir? - They felt it.
無論你在海外遭遇了什么
Whatever happened to you overseas,
你都不必感到內疚或慚愧
there's no reason to feel guilty or ashamed.
我為國盡忠了  我那么做
I served my country. I did what I did...
是因為我別無選擇
because it's what I had to do.
不像某些人
Not like some others.
我成年以來一直擔任公職  威爾
I've been in public office my entire adult life, Will.
其實我曾與你這種人是同學
The truth is, I went to school with guys like you.
英姿颯爽  心懷善意的人
Good looking guys with good intentions...
跟你一樣
just like you.
這是我的真心話
And I mean that sincerely.
我還想讓你知道  無論明天結果如何
And I want you to know that whatever happens tomorrow,
我從未質疑過你的意圖
I never doubted your intentions.
現在對你來說很晚了  總統先生  休息去吧
Must be late for you, Mr. President. Get some sleep.
恐怕我們倆今晚都很難睡得著
I doubt either of us will be getting much sleep tonight.
謝謝你接聽我的電話
But thank you for taking my call.
也謝謝你來電
Well, thank you for calling.
現在只剩下一個問題  一個很重要的問題
Now, there's only one more question, and it's a big one.
只能由你們自己回答
And you're gonna have to answer it yourselves.
誰會成為下任美國總統
Who's gonna be the next President of the United States?
我知道我會投給誰
I know who I'm voting for.
我想感謝辦成這次24小時節目的各位
I'd like to thank everyone who made the last 24 hours possible.
全體技術人員和工作人員
All the... the technicians and crew.
如果我們能像他們一樣齊心協力  那我保證
And if we all work together the way they have, then I promise,
我們真的會為世界上最偉大的國家
we will truly make this the first of many, many new days
開啟嶄新的未來
for the greatest country in the world.
早安  美國  天佑美國  謝謝
Good morning, America. God bless America, and thank you.
下線了  好了  各位
And we're out. Okay, guys.
你很棒
You did great.
-你做到了  -是啊
- You did it. - Yeah.
大家都很滿意
Everyone is so pleased.
我知道很辛苦  但你挺過來了
I know it was tough, but you got through it.
-我很為你驕傲  -謝謝
- I'm really proud of you. - Thank you.
只是些我需要回答的問題
Just some questions that I needed to answer.
我知道  但你做到了  你做到了
I know. But you did it. You did it.
-真棒  -非常棒
- Great job. - That was great.
-很出色  -謝謝
- Amazing. - Thank you.
測試  測試  一  二  三
Testing, testing. One, two, three.
測試  一  二  三
Testing. One, two, three.
稍稍加大增益  混響再強點
A little more gain. A skosh more reverb.
測試  測試  很好  很好
Testing, testing, testing. That's good. That's good.
我想感謝美國人民
I would like to thank the American people
今晚十分踴躍的支持
for their overwhelming support tonight.
作為下任總統  我非常重視這份職責
As your next president, I do not take this mandate lightly.
其實  壓力非常大
In fact... it is heavy as hell.
你倒是比安德伍德更有機會勝選
You got a better chance than Underwood does.
你的高跟鞋很高  布莉姬特
Those are very high heels, Bridget.
安德伍德一敗選  委員會就會解散
When Underwood loses, the committee goes away.
你的話讓我心痛
You're breaking my heart.
我本來還期待
I was looking forward to
聽你說說道格·斯坦普的料
hearing what you had to say about Doug Stamper.
我本來也期待跟你說的
Yeah, I was looking forward to saying it.
我是來道謝的
I came here to thank you.
我從網上撤掉了那個
I took it down... off the Internet.
跟你談這事很奇怪  畢竟
It's weird, talking to you about this. I mean...
你看過
you saw it.
我弟弟本可能看到的
My brother could've seen that.
我會讓你想起你弟弟嗎
Do I remind you of your brother?
他要年輕[當下]一些
He's a little more present.
我的工作是展望未來
Well, it's my job to look ahead.
祝你好運
Good luck with that.
-非常感謝  -謝謝  先生
- Thank you so very much. - Thank you, sir.
我們拿到了昨晚的數據
We have the overnight numbers.
告訴我異常數據
Give me the outliers.
紐約掉了兩個點  新罕布什爾漲了兩個點
Minus two in New York. Plus two in New Hampshire.
都不算壞
Both not bad.
我一直不喜歡"不好不壞"這句話
"Half-empty, half-full" is an expression I have never cared for.
你昨晚的電話有作用
The call you made last night, it's helping.
今早登上了頭條
We grabbed the headlines this morning.
-道格  -是  先生
- Doug? - Yes, sir.
幫我聯系加夫尼的薩莉·安
I want you to reach out to Sally Ann back in Gaffney
告訴我目前的投票率
and get me the turnout so far.
我可以告訴你全州投票率
I can get you the numbers for the state.
我不要全州的  我要加夫尼的投票率
No, I don't want that. I want the Gaffney turnout.
你收到陸續發來的全州數據就給我們
State numbers come in, you give them to us as they come.
任何異常都要告訴我們
Anything out of the ordinary, you let us know.
除此之外  沒其他事了  道格
Other than that, we're done. Oh, and, Doug?
-是  先生  -你知道去哪找我們
- Yes, sir. - You'll know where to find us.
你擔心我們剛看到的選民嗎
You're worried about the crowd we just saw.
不是人數  而是熱情程度
Not the size. Their enthusiasm.
我看不見得
I don't think so.
杰里  我得待會兒回你電話
Jerry, I'm gonna have to call you back.
這份九點的投票率是我們票倉的還是搖擺州的
This 9 a.m. turnout in our base precincts or swing?
票倉的
Base.
該死
Shit.
我的數據不同  你要不要...
I've got different numbers. You're gonna need--
我反復確認過了
I did confirm. Twice.
道格  是我  盡快回我電話
Doug, it's me. Call me as soon as you get this.
你只負責車險還是都有
You handle just automobile insurance or all kinds?
《雙重賠償》
都有  火險  地震險
All kinds. Fire, earthquake,
失竊險  公眾責任險
theft, public liability.
集體險  工業險等等  也即將覆蓋
Group insurance, industrial stuff, and so on right down the line.
意外險
Accident insurance?
意外險  當然  迪特里克森夫人
Accident insurance? Sure, Mrs. Dietrichson.
希望你能告訴我那腳鏈上刻了什么
Wish you'd tell me what's engraved on that anklet.
-我的名字而已  -未請教
- Just my name. - As for instance?
-菲莉斯  -菲莉斯  我想我喜歡這名字
- Phyllis. - Phyllis, huh? I think I like that.
咱們來這段
Let's do this one.
我開車繞著街區來回好多次了
I'd drive it around the block a couple of times.
聶夫先生  不如你明天晚上八點半左右來吧
Mr. Neff, why don't you drop by tomorrow evening around 8:30?
他那時候在家
He'll be in then.
-誰  -我丈夫
- Who? - My husband.
你不是想和他談嗎
You were anxious to talk to him, weren't you?
本來是  但是...
Yeah, I was. But, uh...
我都有點忘記我的來意了  明白我的意思嗎
I'm sort of getting over the idea, if you know what I mean.
這個州有最高車速限制  聶夫先生
There's a speed limit in this state, Mr. Neff.
每小時四十五英里
Forty-five miles an hour.
-我開了多快  警官  -大概每小時九十英里
- How fast was I going, Officer? - I'd say around 90.
看來你要從摩托車上下來  給我開罰單了
Suppose you get off that motorcycle and give me a ticket.
我這次就給你一個警告
So I'd let you off with a warning this time.
如果我不吸取教訓呢
Suppose it doesn't take.
那估計我就得給你一拳了
Suppose I have to whack you over the knuckles.
如果我嚎啕大哭  把頭靠在你肩膀上呢
Suppose I burst out crying and put my head on your shoulder.
如果你把頭靠在我丈夫的肩膀上呢
Suppose you try putting that on my husband's shoulders.
美夢破滅了
That tears it.
我就是沒心情
I'm just not in the mood--
不  拜托  這是傳統
Oh, no. Come on, it's tradition.
如果道格需要我們  他會打電話的
If Doug needs us, he'll call.
是  但是這次不一樣  發生了太多事
Yes, but it's different this time. There's so much going on--
-我知道  就當我迷信吧  -我們在這里
- I know, but call me superstitious. - We're in here.
但我們贏的每一次的選舉都會這么做
But we have done this every election we have ever won.
-拜托  -我不確定我是否明白你的意思
- Come on. - I wonder if I know what you mean.
我不確定你是否真不確定
I wonder if you wonder.
那是一個炎熱的下午  我還記得
It was a hot afternoon, and I still remember
那條街上金銀花的氣味
the smell of honeysuckle all down that street.
我怎么知道謀殺...
How could I have known that murder...
有時聞起來就如金銀花一般
can sometimes smell like honeysuckle?
也許你就會知道  凱耶斯
Maybe you would've known, Keyes,
就在她提到意外險的那一刻
the minute she mentioned accident insurance.
但我沒發覺  我感覺好極了
But I didn't. I felt like a million.
怎么了
Yes.
我回辦公室看我是否有郵件
I went back to the office to see if I had any mail.
什么叫并不相符
Well, what do you mean they don't match?
在我的家鄉
In my home state?
你和莉安最好馬上給我過來
Well, you and LeAnn better get over here right now.
怎么了
What's the matter?
我們今天早上得到的一些選區的數字
There's something wrong with the numbers in the precincts
有些問題  它們并不相符
that we're getting from this morning. They don't match up.
這在南卡羅萊納從沒發生過
It's never happened before in South Carolina.
你沒什么要說的嗎
Well, you have nothing to say about that?
我相信是搞錯了
I'm sure the numbers are wrong.
你才不那么想呢
You don't believe that for a second.
我說不過你
I can't win with you.
不管我說什么
No matter what I say.
你送我回家過幾次
How many times did you walk me home?
什么
What?
不知道  大概就幾次吧
I don't know. Probably a handful.
不  并不是幾次
No, it wasn't a handful.
一個月有18次
It was 18... in a month.
我順路
It was on my way home.
-你什么意思  -沒什么  我正好順路
- And what are you saying? - Nothing. It was on my way home.
不  不是順路
No, it wasn't just on your way home.
我們想去藝術博物館
We tried to go to the Museum of Fine Arts.
-但那兒關門了  那天很冷  -對
- It was closed. It was freezing that day. - Yeah.
-你房間里播著這部電影  -是的
- And this was on in your room. - It was.
我讓你吻我  我逼你吻我
And I asked you to kiss me. I made you kiss me.
不  你沒有逼我吻你  我想吻你的
No, you didn't make me kiss you. I wanted to kiss you.
不管怎樣  我知道我們
And anyway, I knew we were
會攜手共度余生
gonna spend the rest of our lives together.
是的
And we are.
無論如何  絕不后悔
No regrets, no matter what.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
你那是什么意思  "無論如何"
What do you mean by that, "No matter what"?
-你覺得我們會輸  -不
- You think we're gonna lose? - No!
不
No.
我們是一起的嗎
Are we together?
是的  我們是一起的  無論如何
Yes, we're together. No matter what--
不  沒有"無論如何"  我們是一起的嗎
No, not "No matter what." Are we together?
我們是一起的  弗蘭西斯
We're together, Francis.
那就再不要跟我提起失敗了
Then don't ever bring up losing around me again.
-是那個男孩  -謝謝  凱耶斯先生
- That's the boy. - Thank you, Mr. Keyes.
這是家什么公司
What kind of an outfit is this, anyway?
我們是保險公司
Are we an insurance company
還是一群給那種白癡
or just a bunch of dim-witted amateurs
開保單的弱智
to write a policy on a mug like that?
等一下  凱耶斯  他不是我評估的
Now, wait a minute, Keyes. I don't rate this beef.
費城的投票率比他們說的要低
The turnout in Philly is lower than they're saying.
-低多少  -我們的關鍵選區低30%
- How much lower? - 30% in our key precincts.
30  怎么會這樣
Thirty? How?
不只是賓州  大家都沒來投票
It's not just Pennsylvania. People aren't voting.
他們的人  我們的人
Their people, our people.
等等  如果康威拿下了賓州
Wait. If Conway's got Pennsylvania,
那他也會拿下俄亥俄
then he's got Ohio.
如果他拿下俄亥俄  我們就輸了
If he's got Ohio, then we lose.
-這是怎么發生的  -我去告訴他們
- How did this happen? - I'll tell them.
這件事不用你做
That is one thing you are not doing.
都辦妥了
That was all there was to it.
沒有疏忽  沒有忽略
Nothing had slipped, nothing had been overlooked.
沒有什么會暴露我們
There was nothing to give us away.
然而  凱耶斯
And yet, Keyes,
當我沿街走去藥店時
as I was walking down the street to the drugstore,
我突然意識到一切都會出錯
suddenly it came over me that everything would go wrong.
這聽起來有點瘋狂  凱耶斯
It sounds crazy, Keyes,
但這是真的  幫我
but it's true, so help me.
我甚至聽不到自己的腳步聲
I couldn't hear my own footsteps.
就好像一具行尸
It was the walk of a dead man.
那是我度過最長的一夜  凱耶斯
That was the longest night I ever lived through, Keyes.
第二天事情見報后  就更糟了
And the next day was worse when the story broke in the papers.
他們開始在辦公室里談論
They started talking about it at the office.
第三天  你開始調查
And the day after that, when you started digging into it.
我一直把手揣在口袋里
I kept my hands in my pockets
因為我以為它們在顫抖
because I thought they were shaking.
我戴了深色眼鏡好讓別人看不到我的眼睛
I put on dark glasses so people couldn't see my eyes,
然后我又把眼鏡摘了
then I took them off again
他們就不會好奇我為什么要戴了
so they wouldn't get to wondering why I wore them.
-我努力想振作起來  但是...  -謝謝
- I tried to hold myself together but... - Thank you.
我能感覺到我的神經在崩潰
...I could feel my nerves pulling me to pieces.
給我接南卡羅萊納
Get me Sally Ann
切諾基縣書記官薩莉·安
in the Cherokee County clerk's office in South Carolina.
我等著
I'll hold.
他們把賓州的投票率高估了30%
They overestimated the turnouts in Pennsylvania by 30%.
你好啊
Hi, y'all.
不要叫我"閣下"
Well, now, do not call me "Sir."
我是弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
This is Francis Underwood.
我們認識這么久了  不用來這套
We've known each other too long for that.
那么  薩莉  今天的投票率怎么樣
So, Sally, how was turnout today?
我就想知道切諾基郡的數據
Well, I was just really actually looking for Cherokee County.
是的  我只是想親耳聽到
Yes, I just wanted to hear it for myself.
很好  謝謝
Great. Thank you.
代我們跟亨利和孩子們問好
And we send our love to Henry and the boys.
再見
Goodbye.
-有點低  -你說"低"是什么意思
- It's low. - What do you mean, "low"?
就是很低
Low.
我剛在想那條腳鏈
I was thinking about that anklet.
你現在在想什么
And what are you thinking about now?
我不想再想了  寶貝
I'm all through thinking, baby.
我只是過來說再見
I just came to say goodbye.
再見  你要去哪
Goodbye? Where are you going?
要走的是你  寶貝  不是我
You're the one that's going, baby. Not me.
我要在這個街角下電車
I'm getting off the trolley car right at this corner.
別賣關子了  不管是什么  直說吧
Suppose you stop being fancy. Let's have it, whatever it is.
好吧  我來告訴你
All right, I'll tell you.
我一個朋友有個有趣的理論
Friend of mine's got a funny theory...
你知道這意味著什么  是吧
You know what this means, don't you?
這是我們的地盤
This is our house.
我們絕不會離開
We are not leaving.
終點站是個墓地
The last stop's a cemetery.
南北戰爭后  聯邦政府就開始大規模  系統地向退伍軍人提供一系列福利
相關的行政部門經過多次重組  從1930年的胡佛政府開始
退伍軍人相關的福利發放工作  統一由"退伍軍人部"負責
1944年由富蘭克林·羅斯福簽署的《士兵法案》  幾經修改
目前仍是向退伍士兵提供福利的最重要的一個聯邦法案
2017年特朗普政府提交的預算草案中  退伍軍人部的預算為1823億美元
而且美國公眾對軍人也非常尊敬  他們享受很多優待  優惠和優先
但許多軍人從戰場上歸來后  無法適應普通人的生活
發展出精神或心理上的疾病  出現酗酒  吸毒等問題  甚至自殺
而退伍軍人部作為一個龐大的聯邦機構  運作效率低下  官僚之風盛行
屢屢爆出丑聞后  在官僚體制下  一些相關的責任人卻未得到懲處
2017年4月27日  美國總統特朗普簽署行政命令
在退伍軍人部內成立一個新機構  加強對相關事務的監管